Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying roads drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
And thus a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting.
Either way, I'm feeling alive!
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
Raise your flag up high!
Hail a brand new dawn!
Blaze across the sky!
Time to journey on!
On your mark!
Camel of other things!
Well, on Earth, a legendary!
Hooray!
If you can show your breath,
Then we'll make some waves!
We run our daunted!
Ain't no beginners!
Cause if you're wanted,
Then you're a winner!
For we are on the cruise!
And freedom is the only rule!
Fearless night and day!
Cause that's just our way!
Find one piece!
I'll be the first!
I've heard it be so bad!
Just a good verse!
It's all this real!
It must be cause my hand's on a wheel!
I'm done playing, feel it's waiting!
In a world I'm feeling alive!
But I'll be loud!
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
We have come so far!
Gotta make it to the end!
Whatever danger we find!
No one ever left behind!
I've always got your back, my friend!
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward!
Dreaming from the very
first day I'd make my name!
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed!
I'm done playing through with the wave!
In every world I'm feeling alive!
Look out below!
Wake up, sunshine!
And here we go!
We go!
You think you can save them all?
Oh, that's rich.
Rich, you talk a big game,
don't you, Straw Hat?
This is crazy.
He turned his back on deck in two? Sister!
Swim away!
It's up to you to save
our people, Shirahoshi!
It's a bit late for that.
A bit late?
What is that supposed to mean?
Donut, isn't Deccan on the
brink of death right now?
If he dies or passes out, then no
one goes back to normal, right?
His power will go away, and the
ship will stop following her!
And that means...
It'll hit the island!
Why'd you kick me?
That hurt!
Well, you shouldn't have hurt Nami.
You big waste of space.
How about another goose egg to match.
Next time be careful.
Will you drop your fat ass?
Nami.
Please don't get any
scratches on that hot body?
Not another one.
Give me a break.
Watch out! She's dangerous!
Last time she used that magic wand
thing, she did some major damage.
Ha!
Black ball!
What's she doing there?
She must be some kind of witch. A witch?
That's rude, you guys.
How about Enchantress?
That's much nicer.
But it's not magic.
More like advanced
meteorology, you might say.
Uh-oh.
Squirt cloud prize, go!
What the fuck the fuck?
Help me, I'm dying! Stay back!
I can't let you touch me,
hee, or I'll be dried squid!
Icarus,
did you notice how
distraught the black-suited
buffoon was when that
woman fell to the ground?
I believe we may have discovered
his weakness. Oh, yeah!
I'll make sure she can't move.
You can do the gruesome part!
Leave it to me, hee!
See,
if you don't want to get yourself zapped,
you shouldn't be playing with lightning.
Hey, did something just grab me?
Murphy, you can be dried squid instead.
Wait, what's going on?
I can't move.
Somebody help me! Anybody!
Nami?
That's right!
Here you go!
Say hello to the squid spear!
While you're standing
there, could I see your pa -
So you're on their side?
Well, I'm glad I stabbed you then.
I'll drain you dry, he! Huh?
What's the matter?
When my spear stabs you, you're supposed
to bleed out and turn into dry squid!
a skeleton i'm already dry as a bone
But how can that be here jeez
what's the point of having
a bad-ass robot if everybody's
too chicken to fight it
Are you okay boss?
Who are you?
Franky Franky Come on, you
don't know a super guy like me?
Ah, you're one of their
officers, ain't ya?
You should have the backbone
to fight me at least.
I'm a squid, but I've got backbone.
Backbone?
We have that in common.
My brother.
You're such a bonehead.
Hey, skeleton.
I'd move away from there if
I were you. Huh? Why's that?
Just move.
What did I step in?
Um, his face.
Whoa, what's he doing there?
He must have been the reason
I couldn't move my legs.
Oh, hello.
And who might you be?
How did you like that?
Huh?
You've just suffered a
devastating headbutt to your foot.
Uh prepare to enter a world of pain?
Yes any moment now he can't
admit he's getting stepped on!
I'm sorry i stepped on
you he said it oh it's
a special technique i
developed for delivering
a headbutt where you
least expect it i call it
the super soul headbutt
don't give it a name?
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
It's time for some payback. Chomp-chomp!
You're no match for me on the ground.
Now I'm gonna chew you up
and spit you out. Starover!
If you're not careful, there won't be
any ground left for us to stand on.
You don't have to dig
that many tunnels, do you?
Alright!
Hey, Chopper!
You all done?
Need some help out here!
Heh, I bet I can catch this guy off guard.
Oh boy, almost too easy.
I'll rush you into the ground, Gibson!
Usopp, look out!
Horn Cannon, out!
Wow, nice going!
So are all the tunnels connected?
Yep, good to go.
Sweet!
Now, special attack, Green Star!
Wait for it!
Skull Bombgrass!
Too bad for you, Shorty!
We already fought a tunnel digger
back in Alabasta, so we're pros now!
Practice makes perfect,
am I right? Uh-huh.
You trying to make fools out of us?
You screwed up my hard work!
I'm gonna pulverize you
like a little bug you are!
I can do some pulverizing myself!
I'll bite that ugly nose off!
Yeah, it's too bad you can't reach it.
Pack me up here, chopper.
Are you still there?
Uh-oh.
Hey, buddy.
Ready, here.
Someone help. Oh, no!
Let me treat your injuries.
It's okay, dear. Don't cry. Daddy!
But we're here!
You need help!
Damn it, Heart.
These people weren't even armed.
How the hell could you do this to them?
Her Majesty, is she safe now?
I've got no idea.
I wish I did.
But wherever she is, I'm
sure she's fighting for us.
Madam Charlie, what's going
to happen to Fishman Island?
Are we going to die?
Fire! Fire!
Ha.
So desperate.
Stay away from the island, Noah! Please!
Shura Hachi!
If the Noah falls now, it's all over!
No!
She came here!
Stop swimming upward!
Sister!
You have to change your
course before it's too late!
They figured it out.
Shura Hachi! Hey!
Touch Viceroy!
Brother, no!
Ryuboshi!
The plan is set.
Do not interfere.
Hey! Hey! Hold on!
If Deccan dies, his
ability will stop working.
You see, I stabbed him so
that the Noah would fall.
So that's it!
If she keeps swimming straight up,
the ship's just gonna crash
right into the island!
No matter how far away she swims, the
problem's just going to get worse! After her!
We gotta go tell her what to do! Right!
Shura Hachi!
We need Hachi!
Stop right there.
I won't let you ruin this.
It's far too convenient for me.
Without even raising a finger, I
can crush my enemies in one shot,
including your meddlesome crew.
Stay with me.
Shirahoshi, you've got
to swim through the side!
Sister!
She...
she heard you!
Yes?
Useless mermaid, this isn't over.
She's pulling away from the island.
And just in time, too.
You're getting on my nerves.
I'll make you pay for that.
I don't think so!
You brat!
You're not gonna hurt, Weepy Hachi!
Watch me!
Noah, please follow me!
I can't hold him!
Just a little further! This way!
Let's go!
Anderdak, would you just
hurry up and die already?
Heart, I'll get my revenge!
Whatever it takes.
If I stop, I will be killed.
The ship, it's starting
to move to the side.
Yeah, you're doing great.
Almost there.
Keep swimming.
Hurry.
My left hand touched you.
So.
You're going to be my final target.
I'll run you into the ground.
I will chase you.
To the gates of hell.
You mustn't give up now Shirahoshi.
If it misses the island?
that this was all for nothing.
Even if I die, you can't escape.
We were too late!
It's folly!
It's right on target, too.
They're all going to die!
Is there nothing we can do?
It can't be!
Now this island will bring in a new era!
Yeah!
So he finally gave up the coast
now his ability will lose its
effect which means the noah is
about to come plummeting down
this is the end star hats for
you and for all those who stood
in the way of my vengeance what
are we gonna do now i don't know?
Surely there must be some
way to stop the ship?
Perhaps!
But even if you could stop it you would
still have to go through me first!
We'll stop you!
If the noah falls it spells
the end for our kingdom!
And the hundreds of years
that were spent protecting
that legendary vessel will
have been all for naught!
Listen well my sons!
The ship of promise, Noah, is
much more than some ancient relic.
Centuries ago,
a promise was made to a great man, and
for our people to keep that promise,
the Noah is not to be moved from the
sea floor until the time is right.
Even today,
there is still much we do
not know about this ship,
including the means by
which it was constructed.
And yet, until its purpose is
served, it must be protected.
It will, Father.
I swear, you needn't worry.
We will find out why it was
moved and set this matter right.
It's not enough to save my people.
I must save the Noah as well.
But whatever happened to that unfounded
bravado of yours? What a joke!
I'm not done!
I'm going to tear that thing
to pieces before it hits land!
No, you mustn't do that!
Even if you do have enough
strength to destroy it,
the Noah has a long history and its
destined purpose is still unfulfilled.
There's no time.
You got a better way to
save the island, huh?
My friends will die.
What's more important,
that boat or your people?
It's possible that Deccan
is simply unconscious.
If we wake him up,
we may have just enough time to
redirect the Noah before it's too late.
Then what if he's dead?
Then how are we going to stop it?
We've got to destroy the ship.
Why can't you just stop and think
things through not getting along
are we well while you're arguing
just know your time is running out
This Man Karate!
Shirozi!
And Sea Drums!
Are you okay, brother? Bomboshi!
Don't eat for a moment,
I've forgotten about you!
This Man Karate!
Knock it off!
Move aside, boy!
Second gear!
Don't go!
Help me, no!
No, jet pistol!
Damn it.
The armament Huang protects
me against punches.
But I guess this is too much.
Gotta watch out for those teeth.
Being underwater is not helping me either.
Only one way to beat this guy.
Now let's go!
So the little coward wants
to fight me on the Noah.
Right, cause there's air on the deck!
Smart move, but I'm still smarter.
Get in there, I can beat
him with the one hit!
I knew it, he's cutting through.
Oh, no.
So sorry to burst your bubble Straw Hat.
That's no good.
How am I going to beat him
if I can't even breathe?
You humans are nearly so tough
when you're out of your element.
You're even weaker than a fish
out of water, one might say.
If you're no match for me, how
can you hope to stop the Noah?
It's over.
Time to say goodbye!
What happened?
I'm here.
Forgive me if that was rough.
Whip Hachi, hey!
Fukaboshi asked me to
help you in his stead.
He's gonna fight?
this is sick what did those
people ever do to you what
kind of heartless person values
life so little what are they
doing I'm not too proud to
admit even though your power was
falsely acquired I wasn't strong
enough to vanquish you But,
still, I have hope.
Combat Combat Ultra Marie Technique!
What I don't understand, Heart,
is how you can seek to destroy so many of
your fellow men and still feel nothing.
What is it you want
that's worth killing for?
What do you stand to gain if Fishman
Island ceases to be? Stop this!
I'll start later! Oh really? Farewell.
You've got to see me!
Mark my words.
Your ill-gotten stripe will never best me.
A little late to be saved.
Forty?
What's happened to you?
At first, you wanted our people
to rise up against humans.
This makes sense, even if it's misguided.
But now you would have
the entire population
of Fishman Island be put to death instead!
There are people living in the Fishman
District who were once your allies!
What you're doing doesn't
benefit anyone, not even you!
Why can't you see that, Heart?
Is there something I don't know?
Or is your hatred so deep that you've
abandoned your sense of reason entirely?
Tell me the cause of this madness.
Did humans attack you?
Did they torment you
in some untold manner?
Did they kill your friends?
Did they hurt your family?
Did they take something you hold dear?
Answer me, dammit!
What did humans do to you
that was so unforgivable?
Why?
What in this world could
inspire such cruelty?
I don't
know.
Please don't die!
We be Hachi.
Strawhead Luffy, this is the air tank.
We've met before, remember?
Oh, yeah, hey guys.
We've been listening to
what's happening out there.
And we can see the Noah
hurtling toward the island.
We've begun making the
preparations as we've discussed.
So that's what Brother Hachi meant before.
I've got business there, too.
What is this?
Huh?
Aren't you gonna go? Not yet.
We must be cautious.
But if we don't follow
him, he'll get away!
Horty's obviously up to something here.
And more importantly, we have to be
ready to face him underwater again.
Stay alert.
So what do we do?
I have an idea.
Where are we up to?
Brother Hachi!
Prince Fukaboshi?
What brings you here?
It's quite possible that we're going to
need a large amount of air very soon.
Please make arrangements for us. Sir!
I can handle this.
There's supposed to be some
air on the deck, right?
If I could breathe, there's no problem.
Deccan needs the bubble.
That much is true.
However, Heart may still destroy
it if worse comes to worse.
Take this baby transponder snail.
This will be our last resort in
the event that things go poorly.
We must be prepared for anything.
Oh, Luffy, I don't know what to do.
Hey, guys, what do we need to
do to get a little air from you?
We can shoot out all
the air in the air tank.
What's that thing for, anyway?
It's an air conditioning facility
that provides air for Fishman Island.
If we create a big bubble and shoot
it, maybe it'll surround the NOAA.
However,
the bubble would neutralize
ascending forces,
so it's not going to make the
NOAA stop or reverse course.
On top of that,
we'd have to use all the air we've got to
make the bubble big
enough to hold the ship,
and it would crash long
before we could resupply.
What I mean is we've got only one chance.
If we don't manage to
send out the bubble at the
exact moment the NOAA moves
closest to the air tank,
Ben, we're done. It's over.
All riding on one shot, huh?
Wow, better not miss. Right.
I'm afraid that's all we can do.
After we deploy the bubble,
the rest is up to you.
I should reiterate, this is...
Don't make it more complicated.
Just go for it, okay?
If I can breathe, I'll make this work.
All right, roger that.
We'll do our best not to miss the ship.
And Luffy, everyone
here is counting on you.
They're swimming alongside it.
You're just a lowly human
and a cowardly mermaid.
What can you two possibly
hope to accomplish now?
Shark Traitor!
Out of my way.
Superman Horsing!
No way!
He got even bigger!
Ready to give up?
You should be human.
Just the sight of you vile worms
makes me sick to my stomach.
Even if it shortens my life,
and even if I have to sacrifice
everything in this world,
I swear to you, I will have my
revenge against the human race.
Heart!
You've only got one shot,
so you better not miss it.
If this doesn't work, the
whole island's done for?
Can you hear me, Straw Hat?
Oh dear, that's my brother's
voice Hey, buddy, are you okay?
I'm barely alive, but please listen.
He spoke earlier and...
It's clear now who he is.
Yeah.